Privacy Policy

###### Dezgo

* * *

* * *

[Text-to-video \[BETA\]](https://dezgo.com/text2video)

* * *

powered by Stable Diffusion AI  
[Terms](https://dezgo.com/terms) - [Privacy](https://dezgo.com/privacy) - [Open RAIL-M License](https://dezgo.com/license)  
Privacy Manager

\- **The cutting-edge [Flux model](https://dezgo.com/model/flux_1_schnell) is now available on Dezgo!** Enjoy better prompt adherence, improved image quality for different image styles and the ability to generate text.  
\- To celebrate, use the **FLUXGO5** coupon for a $5 discount on orders of at least $20 until Sep 16.  
\- **Win up to $100 in Dezgo credits** by sharing your best Flux-generated images on our Discord contest here: [Join now](https://discord.gg/UHfTvFt9)

### Privacy Policy

This is Dezgo SAS Privacy Policy for Dezgo.com. This document explains Dezgo SAS policies for the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information on Dezgo.com. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by this site.

#### COLLECTION OF DATA

As on many websites, the site editor may automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if it is indeed the site editor's policy to display advertising) is set forth below.

#### USE OF DATA

Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data from being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site editor's policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site editor to protect the site editor's legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this policy. In the event you choose to use links displayed on this website to visit other websites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites. Dezgo SAS uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

#### COOKIES

Like many websites, this website sets and uses cookies to enhance your user experience — to remember your personal settings, for instance. Advertisements may display on this website and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties providing the advertising do not have access to this site's cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site. For more information about this type of online advertising, about cookies, and about how to turn this feature off, [please visit this link](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/). Please note that turning off advertising cookies won’t mean that you are not served any advertising, merely that it will not be tailored to your interests.

#### ADVERTISING

This Site is affiliated with Freestar for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and Freestar will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Freestar's data usage, click here: [https://freestar.com/privacy-policy/](https://freestar.com/privacy-policy/).

An error has occurred. This application may need to be reloaded. Reload Dismiss
